{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"38\u00d742=","answer":"1596.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":" ( 11 * 17) + 56=","answer":"243.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"log 10(797)=","answer":"2.9015","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"-1-9=","answer":"-10.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"936913097197+52653430976=","answer":"989566528173.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"6152\u00d732179=","answer":"197965208.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"log 2(432)=","answer":"8.7549","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"3**3=","answer":"27.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"8+56=","answer":"64.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"13+934=","answer":"947.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"log 10(495)=","answer":"2.6946","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"tan(9.17\u03c0)=","answer":"0.5774","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"pi-\u03c0=","answer":"0.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"85\u00d747=","answer":"3995.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"cos(-9.75\u03c0)=","answer":"0.7071000000000001","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"33\/22=","answer":"1.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"0.09*2.0=","answer":"0.18","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"9+2=","answer":"11.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"cos(-60\u00b0)=","answer":"0.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"51677\u00d790778=","answer":"4691134706.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"ln(247)=","answer":"5.5094","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"e-5=","answer":"-2.2817","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"4.3651^3.1882=","answer":"109.7563","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"50\/95=","answer":"0.5263","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"4-10=","answer":"-6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"50\/18=","answer":"2.7778","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"88254\u00d726228=","answer":"2314725912.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"721-847=","answer":"-126.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"714637232158-667119914538=","answer":"47517317620.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"0.0069+(-0.86)=","answer":"-0.8531000000000001","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"-4+(-6)=","answer":"-10.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"5+2=","answer":"7.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":" 38 + ( 26 \/ 67) * 19=","answer":"45.3731","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"ln(779)=","answer":"6.658","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"6+2=","answer":"8.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"10+(-3)=","answer":"7.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"2\u00d789=","answer":"178.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"88.0+(-0.54)=","answer":"87.46","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"70\u00f761=","answer":"1.1475","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"2+6=","answer":"8.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"14\u00f785=","answer":"0.1647","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"sin(-0.5\u03c0)=","answer":"-1.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":" ( 14 + 96) * 93 + ( 72 * 23)=","answer":"11886.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"ln(695)=","answer":"6.5439","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"0.6\u00d74.0=","answer":"2.4","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"5.0*0.09=","answer":"0.45","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"66\u00d745=","answer":"2970.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"-23.0-(-0.43)=","answer":"-22.57","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"373490079876-646750175965=","answer":"-273260096089.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"7^4=","answer":"2401.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"71786\u00d721638=","answer":"1553305468.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"623690866796+368029869233=","answer":"991720736029.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"e-pi=","answer":"-0.4232","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"3**4=","answer":"81.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"5^4=","answer":"625.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"2-8=","answer":"-6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"71\/22=","answer":"3.2273","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"636+766=","answer":"1402.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"420-6=","answer":"414.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":" 32 \/ 15=","answer":"2.1333","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"5655\u00d742805=","answer":"242062275.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"774426524175+721318944497=","answer":"1495745468672.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -32, -28, -22, -14, -4?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 28, 76, 170, 334, 592?","answer":"968","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 97, 178, 259?","answer":"340","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 199, 408, 617, 826?","answer":"1035","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 219, 201, 181, 159, 135, 109, 81?","answer":"51","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 34, 61, 88, 115?","answer":"142","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 10, 21, 38, 61, 90, 125?","answer":"166","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -731, -732, -733?","answer":"-734","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 5929, 5928, 5927, 5926, 5925, 5924?","answer":"5923","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -321, -330, -351, -390, -453?","answer":"-546","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -1691, -1690, -1689, -1688?","answer":"-1687","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -27, -52, -69, -78, -79, -72, -57?","answer":"-34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 219, 437, 655, 873, 1091, 1309?","answer":"1527","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 50, 62, 92, 146, 230, 350, 512?","answer":"722.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -609, -1186, -1763, -2340, -2917, -3494?","answer":"-4071","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -71, -79, -101, -143, -211, -311, -449?","answer":"-631","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 244, 253, 262?","answer":"271","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -40, -49, -70, -109, -172?","answer":"-265.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 17, 34, 51, 68?","answer":"85","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 1964, 3923, 5880, 7835?","answer":"9788","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 35, 123, 271, 479, 747, 1075?","answer":"1463.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 20, 31, 46, 65?","answer":"88.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -53, -114, -175?","answer":"-236","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 3, -23, -51, -81?","answer":"-113","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 61, 62, 53, 28, -19?","answer":"-94","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: -396, -392, -378, -348, -296?","answer":"-216","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 1070, 4273, 9610, 17081?","answer":"26686","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 1927, 1929, 1929, 1927, 1923?","answer":"1917","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 6, 43, 140, 327, 634, 1091, 1728, 2575?","answer":"3662","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -109, -391, -859, -1513?","answer":"-2353","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 80, 75, 68, 59, 48, 35?","answer":"20","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 2538, 2528, 2504, 2460, 2390, 2288, 2148?","answer":"1964","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 30, 52, 74, 96?","answer":"118","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 273, 545, 821, 1101, 1385, 1673?","answer":"1965","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -1088, -1086, -1082, -1076, -1068, -1058?","answer":"-1046","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 5, 18, 31, 44, 57?","answer":"70","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -29, -77, -125, -173, -221, -269?","answer":"-317","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -388, -386, -384?","answer":"-382","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 140, 177, 250, 365, 528, 745, 1022, 1365?","answer":"1780","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: -75, -80, -85, -90?","answer":"-95","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 1, 22, 43, 64, 85, 106?","answer":"127","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 894, 886, 864, 822, 754?","answer":"654","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -42, -228, -538, -972, -1530, -2212, -3018?","answer":"-3948","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -93, -96, -77, -24, 75, 232, 459, 768?","answer":"1171","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -117, -231, -345, -459, -573?","answer":"-687","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 369, 372, 375, 378?","answer":"381","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -1, -2, 1, 8, 19?","answer":"34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -24, -35, -50, -69, -92, -119, -150?","answer":"-185.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 49, 75, 95, 109, 117, 119, 115?","answer":"105","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 114, 227, 340, 453, 566?","answer":"679.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 1833, 1837, 1841, 1845, 1849?","answer":"1853","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -262, -1052, -2360, -4180, -6506, -9332, -12652, -16460?","answer":"-20750","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 11, 17, 27, 41, 59?","answer":"81","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 12, 24, 38, 54, 72, 92, 114?","answer":"138","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -29, -46, -81, -140, -229, -354?","answer":"-521","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 17, 49, 129, 281, 529, 897, 1409?","answer":"2089","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 5313, 5311, 5309, 5307, 5305, 5303?","answer":"5301","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 16, 33, 50, 67?","answer":"84","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 40, 54, 80, 124, 192, 290?","answer":"424","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 8, 48, 128, 260, 456, 728, 1088?","answer":"1548","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 38, 52, 70, 86, 94, 88?","answer":"62.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 44, 39, 32, 23?","answer":"12","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Put together -758 and -1.","answer":"-759.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -8699 less than -0.3?","answer":"8698.7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out 608.4 + -0.04.","answer":"608.36","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add -2.517873 and -0.04.","answer":"-2.557873","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out 0.53 - 1187.45.","answer":"-1186.92","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add -0.8904 and -3.79.","answer":"-4.6804","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Calculate -1455 - -0.095.","answer":"-1454.905","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Put together -108241 and -0.2.","answer":"-108241.2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -2 - 16439?","answer":"-16441.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Total of -0.022 and -24.","answer":"-24.022","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"11326848+-0.1","answer":"11326847.9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out -0.152 + -5.74.","answer":"-5.892","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -0.1 less than 1115205.8?","answer":"1115205.9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Subtract 0.0322 from 0.","answer":"-0.0322","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 0.3245 less than -7?","answer":"-7.3245","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Subtract -3828 from -0.1.","answer":"3827.9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add together 4 and 0.086612.","answer":"4.086612","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Sum -8197.457 and -4.","answer":"-8201.457","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"2.26 - 0.016","answer":"2.244","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"-11 - -0.0479186","answer":"-10.9520814","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 34 plus -931?","answer":"-897.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 5.8 plus 73.95?","answer":"79.75","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between 0.189 and 14.26?","answer":"14.071","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -161 plus 1124?","answer":"963.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between 813 and -82?","answer":"895.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"-0.1+507.39","answer":"507.29","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add together -18.766737 and -0.5.","answer":"-19.266737","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between 0.7 and -1843?","answer":"1843.7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add together 2585 and -13.","answer":"2572.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -74366 take away -0.05?","answer":"-74365.95","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add together -7.734 and -0.18.","answer":"-7.914","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add together 0.05 and -0.04463.","answer":"0.00537","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 1 + -8193?","answer":"-8192.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -0.1 + -9208?","answer":"-9208.1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"52.21 + 0.5","answer":"52.71","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -2 less than 2.63353?","answer":"4.63353","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"-37.5+0.24","answer":"-37.26","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out -1 - -0.0553.","answer":"-0.9447","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 7 less than 0.00533?","answer":"-6.99467","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -6.5 + -1.5?","answer":"-8.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 5090 + 3?","answer":"5093.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out 8.2269 - 0.4.","answer":"7.8269","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Put together -2158 and -4.","answer":"-2162.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -0.02199 take away -0.5?","answer":"0.47801","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the difference between -54 and -1340?","answer":"1286.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the difference between -1.8 and -0.74?","answer":"1.06","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out 4 - 58325.","answer":"-58321.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -0.573395 plus 0.2?","answer":"-0.373395","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Sum 39.85 and -183.","answer":"-143.15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 221 take away 0.2?","answer":"220.8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Add together -0.269 and -0.0416.","answer":"-0.3106","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 10203 - -0.0259?","answer":"10203.0259","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between -7.077 and -45?","answer":"37.923","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the difference between -5 and -52887?","answer":"52882.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Subtract -1 from -467.","answer":"-466.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Calculate 422 - 121.","answer":"301.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Calculate 0.09 - 428.","answer":"-427.91","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"18446+529","answer":"18975.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"-0.5 + -6.2084","answer":"-6.7084","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -112 + -16312?","answer":"-16424.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is 7825 minus -0.03?","answer":"7825.03","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -84217 minus -5?","answer":"-84212.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of -4 + -1 + -6 - -12?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate (-2 - (0 + -1)) + 3.","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate -4 + 0 - ((-3 - -1) + 7).","answer":"-9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of -2 + 4 - (-4 + 2 + -1)?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-5 - (3 + -6) - -3) + 0?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is -12 + (1 + 5 - -1) - -4?","answer":"-1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate 11 - (25 + -16) - (-1 + 3).","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate -8 + 1 + -63 + 67 - -3.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of 1 - (7 + (15 + -9 - 6))?","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 8 + -1 - (-3 + 8).","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of (1 - -1) + -2 + 1?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of -3 + -12 + 2 + 7?","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is -4 - (-11 + 8) - -9?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 19 - (13 + -12 + 7).","answer":"11.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 2 + 5 + 0 + -3 + -1.","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"-1 + -2 + -1 + 0","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"-7 + 0 + 5 + -6 - -4","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of 1 - 0 - 4 - (-3 - -5)?","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"17 - ((-4 - -27) + -10)","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 1 - (-2 - -2) - 6.","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate -13 - -8 - -9 - -1.","answer":"5.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"(-4 - (2 - 3)) + 4","answer":"1.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-17 - -5 - -2) + 2?","answer":"-8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of 5 + (3 + 1 - (-2 - -6))?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of (2 - 22) + -1 + 13 + -3?","answer":"-11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 3 + -4 + 0 + 4 + -7.","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"0 - 2 - (4 - (-5 + 11))","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 1 - (4 - 8 - -8).","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"-7 + (17 - (-8 + 14))","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"6 + -5 - 3 - -8","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is -1 - (2 + 1 - 4)?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is -8 + (12 - -1) - 12?","answer":"-7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate (0 - -1) + (-2 - -4) - 0.","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate (-2 - (9 + -8)) + 3.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate -5 - -2 - -5 - 3.","answer":"-1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"0 + (0 - (-1 - (-6 - 1)))","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"(-4 - -4) + (2 - 1) + 2","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 0 - ((0 - 2) + (11 - 9)).","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 1 - 0 - (-3 - (-1 + 0))?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"-8 + (6 - -8) - (2 - 1)","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate 6 + -9 + (-2 - -4 - 4).","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 7 - (-59 + 65 - (-7 - 0))?","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"2 + -4 - 4 - -4","answer":"-2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"4 - 8 - -6 - 6","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate (0 - 6) + (-2 - -4) + 3.","answer":"-1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 4 - (-5 - -5) - 1?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 5 + 2 + -4 + (1 - 3).","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate (-11 - -6) + 7 - 5.","answer":"-3.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 1 + -3 - (25 - (38 - 10))?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 9 - 2 - 11 - (-1 - 1)?","answer":"-2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"4 - (8 + -6 + 5)","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"1 + 0 - ((3 - 9) + 2)","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 2 - (-6 + -2 + 5)?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate 6 + 5 + (4 - 10).","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate (3 - (-4 - -3)) + -4.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"-1 + 6 + (9 - 10)","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is (-10 - -6) + (-5 - -3)?","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"(5 - 12) + (7 - -5)","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Evaluate (-6 - -2) + (5 - 3) - 2.","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is (-2 + (-3 - -8) - 1) + -1?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate -2 - (4 - 3) - 2.","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate -8 + 3 - (1 + -4 - 0).","answer":"-2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 171 by -2.","answer":"-171\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -19 divided by 19.","answer":"-1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -238 divided by -3.","answer":"238\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 64 by 2.","answer":"32","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 0 divided by -53?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 105 divided by -1.","answer":"-105","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 2448 divided by 2?","answer":"1224","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 1272 divided by -159?","answer":"-8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"2 divided by 31","answer":"2\/31","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 1 divided by 36.","answer":"1\/36","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -11 divided by -5?","answer":"11\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 96 by -15.","answer":"-32\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"13415 divided by -4","answer":"-13415\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -476 divided by -4.","answer":"119","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 494 divided by -2?","answer":"-247","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"15 divided by -3","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 0 divided by -3814?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 4236 divided by 706.","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -133 divided by 4.","answer":"-133\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 8 divided by 1?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 360 divided by -120?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -1959 by -1.","answer":"1959","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -1223 divided by -2?","answer":"1223\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"-140 divided by -28","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 3 by -1333.","answer":"-3\/1333","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 1111 divided by 1111.","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"29 divided by 3","answer":"29\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"-2360 divided by -472","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 2595 divided by -15?","answer":"-173","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -9582 divided by 3.","answer":"-3194","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -3 divided by -125.","answer":"3\/125","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 109 divided by -37.","answer":"-109\/37","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -1 divided by -121.","answer":"1\/121","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -1356 by 4.","answer":"-339","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -513 by 19.","answer":"-27","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -11451 by 3.","answer":"-3817","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 179 divided by 34?","answer":"179\/34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -852 divided by -3?","answer":"284","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -216 by 3.","answer":"-72","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 2564 divided by -1.","answer":"-2564","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 2046 divided by -5.","answer":"-2046\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 360 by -15.","answer":"-24","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"617 divided by 3","answer":"617\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -716 divided by -5.","answer":"716\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 5 divided by -78?","answer":"-5\/78","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate 23 divided by 2.","answer":"23\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 0 divided by 5?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -4120 divided by 4?","answer":"-1030","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -450 divided by -50?","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"-60 divided by 20","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 9 divided by 4?","answer":"9\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"-4 divided by 94","answer":"-2\/47","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 0 by 274.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 2 divided by -16?","answer":"-1\/8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is 1467 divided by -489?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -236 divided by -59?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"What is -9805 divided by -5?","answer":"1961","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -55 divided by -5.","answer":"11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -1028 by -4.","answer":"257","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"-11 divided by -13","answer":"11\/13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -822 by -2.","answer":"411","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -29 by -584.","answer":"29\/584","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of 72 and -0.4?","answer":"-28.8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-1.3*-173","answer":"224.9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out 5 * 354.","answer":"1770.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate 2252*-0.2.","answer":"-450.4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of 0.5 and -0.45?","answer":"-0.225","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-0.1 times -50","answer":"5.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-0.01*-155","answer":"1.55","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"6 times -4","answer":"-24.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-133 * 13","answer":"-1729.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out -0.9 * 2.36.","answer":"-2.124","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is 1247 times 0.5?","answer":"623.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-11.5*-4","answer":"46","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Multiply 67 and 1.26.","answer":"84.42","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"0.03*3.1","answer":"0.093","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of -129 and -2.8?","answer":"361.2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate 0.04*11.9.","answer":"0.476","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is 24 times -148?","answer":"-3552.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of 2 and -110.1?","answer":"-220.2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"4*1.31","answer":"5.24","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is 5 times -34?","answer":"-170","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-0.047 * -0.063","answer":"0.002961","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is -7 times -271?","answer":"1897.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate 278*0.5.","answer":"139.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate 13*314.","answer":"4082.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"359*92","answer":"33028.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-0.4*0.0989","answer":"-0.03956","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-45 * 66","answer":"-2970.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Multiply -6 and -0.046.","answer":"0.276","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate 163*0.02.","answer":"3.26","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-1.6297 times 1","answer":"-1.6297","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"90.2 * 0.04","answer":"3.608","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of -776.5 and -0.1?","answer":"77.65","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"0.00155 * -0.4","answer":"-0.00062","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out 0.048 * -0.14.","answer":"-0.00672","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"4.1*0.763","answer":"3.1283","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Product of -232 and 2.","answer":"-464","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is 2.62 times 0.1?","answer":"0.262","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-47*0.04","answer":"-1.88","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-0.5 * 540","answer":"-270.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of 0.3 and -81?","answer":"-24.3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate -111*4.","answer":"-444.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is -33 times 0.5?","answer":"-16.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of -41.8 and 4?","answer":"-167.2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is -0.01765 times 0.5?","answer":"-0.008825","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-242*-1","answer":"242.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is -11 times -10?","answer":"110.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is -1.3 times 74?","answer":"-96.2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out -3230 * -5.","answer":"16150","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-4449*0.5","answer":"-2224.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out -35.35 * -0.3.","answer":"10.605","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Multiply -3.08 and 4.","answer":"-12.32","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out -220 * 0.2.","answer":"-44.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is 63 times -0.2?","answer":"-12.6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-2167 times 3","answer":"-6501.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"1006 times 6","answer":"6036.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is 427 times 0?","answer":"0.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is -26.9 times -0.16?","answer":"4.304","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-23*28","answer":"-644.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"2.9 times 13","answer":"37.7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-0.0201 times -0.32","answer":"0.006432","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"-58*-12","answer":"696.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Multiply -0.0756 and 0.14.","answer":"-0.010584","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"((-37)\/407)\/((-1)\/11)","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate ((-1)\/4*-1)\/((-6)\/(-8)).","answer":"1\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate 2\/(2\/(-3))*(-40)\/(-160).","answer":"-3\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (44\/(-66))\/(2\/(-15))?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is 6\/(-21)*56\/(-72)?","answer":"2\/9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate (-4)\/((-24)\/(-2))*-12.","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"((-4)\/(-42))\/((-22)\/(-66))","answer":"2\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate -1*(-12)\/(-8)*22\/(-99).","answer":"1\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of 3\/(-4)*(-928)\/(-174)?","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-2)\/(-4)*128\/(-32)?","answer":"-2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate (8\/(-12))\/(-2)*-3.","answer":"-1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"9*3\/378*6","answer":"3\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate (-2)\/((242\/99)\/(-11)).","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of 24\/16*(-12)\/153?","answer":"-2\/17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-4)\/(8\/(-2))*-5?","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (69\/(-575))\/((-2)\/5)?","answer":"3\/10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate 0*((-27)\/(-6))\/9.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-3*(-7)\/(-42))\/(1\/(-6))?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is (-6*(-5)\/(-10))\/1?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate (-1)\/(-14)*-5*8\/(-10).","answer":"2\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"2\/(-3*1\/(-6))","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate ((-50)\/1125)\/((-2)\/(-10)).","answer":"-2\/9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"(28\/(-21))\/(20\/10)","answer":"-2\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate ((-2)\/25)\/(((-207)\/90)\/(-23)).","answer":"-4\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"108\/(-162)*((-18)\/(-14))\/(-3)","answer":"2\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate 80\/(-32)*(-8)\/(-5).","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is (-1)\/18*-15*3\/10?","answer":"1\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate -5*(2\/8)\/(1\/4).","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-180)\/(-1200)*(-16)\/6?","answer":"-2\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate ((-65)\/(-52))\/((-1)\/(-4)).","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate (8\/(-12))\/((-14)\/(-21)*-1).","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is 24\/(-8)*2\/(-2)?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"-1*(-8)\/(-220)*-5","answer":"2\/11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is ((-8)\/(-12))\/(9\/(162\/28))?","answer":"3\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate (9\/(-16))\/((-30)\/40)*-8.","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate (7\/(-4))\/(((-155)\/20)\/31).","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate 6\/12*-5*-2.","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is ((-4)\/6)\/((-2)\/12)?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-2)\/(-3)*(-153)\/34?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is ((7\/(-3))\/7)\/(2\/18)?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of ((-12)\/14)\/(11\/(308\/(-40)))?","answer":"3\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate (-4)\/(720\/4)*6.","answer":"-2\/15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"(-8)\/14*(-9)\/72*-4","answer":"-2\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate -2*(12\/4)\/3.","answer":"-2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (196\/833)\/((-14)\/(-17))?","answer":"2\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate (-6)\/(96\/16)*(-2)\/(-10).","answer":"-1\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"(-2)\/(-12)*12\/((-12)\/3)","answer":"-1\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"2\/(3*20\/15)*-6","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate ((-16)\/(-12))\/((-2)\/3).","answer":"-2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is 8\/(-54)*(-18)\/(-4)?","answer":"-2\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of ((-2)\/(-5*5\/(-25)))\/(-6)?","answer":"1\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate ((3\/(-1))\/3)\/5.","answer":"-1\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is (6\/((-18)\/3))\/(18\/(-24))?","answer":"4\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate 6*(98\/(-21))\/7.","answer":"-4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Calculate 10\/(-4)*570\/475.","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of (-9)\/27*(-6)\/(-8)?","answer":"-1\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of ((-10)\/(-1))\/5*(-6)\/4?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of 4*(-10)\/(-16)*(-88)\/(-55)?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is 4\/10*(-55)\/176*4?","answer":"-1\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of ((-25)\/8)\/(-5)*(-2)\/5?","answer":"-1\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is (-6)\/(-3)*-1*6\/15?","answer":"-4\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate 2\/(-6)*(-120)\/(-80).","answer":"-1\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -34, -1.1, 1 in decreasing order.","answer":"1, -1.1, -34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -0.5, 9, 1 in descending order.","answer":"9, 1, -0.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -6, 7, 3, -3.","answer":"-6, -3, 3, 7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -4\/27, 0.2, -0.2 in decreasing order.","answer":"0.2, -4\/27, -0.2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -2, 3, -282 in decreasing order.","answer":"3, -2, -282","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -2, 4, -5, 6, -6 in ascending order.","answer":"-6, -5, -2, 4, 6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -27, -2, 0 in ascending order.","answer":"-27, -2, 0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 5, 181, -5 in descending order.","answer":"181, 5, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -5, -11, -10 in descending order.","answer":"-5, -10, -11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 1\/14, 2\/27, -3\/7 in ascending order.","answer":"-3\/7, 1\/14, 2\/27","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 42, -0.2, -0.1, -1 in descending order.","answer":"42, -0.1, -0.2, -1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -0.5, 3, 2, -0.4 in descending order.","answer":"3, 2, -0.4, -0.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 3, -6, -268 in decreasing order.","answer":"3, -6, -268","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 0, 415, 4, -4, -5 in ascending order.","answer":"-5, -4, 0, 4, 415","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -1\/2, 3, 4\/5, 0.4, -79\/14.","answer":"-79\/14, -1\/2, 0.4, 4\/5, 3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 8, -0.4, -1, -0.5 in decreasing order.","answer":"8, -0.4, -0.5, -1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 1020, 5, -5, 2 in decreasing order.","answer":"1020, 5, 2, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -23, -1, 1 in decreasing order.","answer":"1, -1, -23","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -24\/13, 0.4, -3, 2\/3 in descending order.","answer":"2\/3, 0.4, -24\/13, -3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -146, 4, 3, 2, 8 in decreasing order.","answer":"8, 4, 3, 2, -146","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -5, 4, 50 in decreasing order.","answer":"50, 4, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -17, -4, 3, 14.","answer":"-17, -4, 3, 14","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 0, -0.2, -2\/23, 1\/2, -10 in descending order.","answer":"1\/2, 0, -2\/23, -0.2, -10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -6, 4, 588, -3, -2 in increasing order.","answer":"-6, -3, -2, 4, 588","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 29, 3, -17 in descending order.","answer":"29, 3, -17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -8, 8, -3 in descending order.","answer":"8, -3, -8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 1, 18, 9, 4, -5 in descending order.","answer":"18, 9, 4, 1, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 52, -2, -5 in descending order.","answer":"52, -2, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -0.043, 5, 4, -5.","answer":"-5, -0.043, 4, 5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 27, -9, 4, -1 in decreasing order.","answer":"27, 4, -1, -9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 6, -5, -5\/6, 14\/9 in increasing order.","answer":"-5, -5\/6, 14\/9, 6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 6, 2, 1 in decreasing order.","answer":"6, 2, 1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 3, -1, -5, -107.","answer":"-107, -5, -1, 3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 1\/17, 1\/5, -4, 0.11 in increasing order.","answer":"-4, 1\/17, 0.11, 1\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 59, -4, 2, -3, 37 in descending order.","answer":"59, 37, 2, -3, -4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -371, 3, -0.4.","answer":"-371, -0.4, 3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -1\/6, -0.4, -1\/7, 0.3 in descending order.","answer":"0.3, -1\/7, -1\/6, -0.4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 14, 1\/8, -1, -28 in descending order.","answer":"14, 1\/8, -1, -28","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -5, 7, 3, -12 in decreasing order.","answer":"7, 3, -5, -12","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -3, 99, -11 in decreasing order.","answer":"99, -3, -11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 3, 4, -4, -1 in increasing order.","answer":"-4, -1, 3, 4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 0, -4, 5, -5, 2 in decreasing order.","answer":"5, 2, 0, -4, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -11, 1\/2, -1\/3 in descending order.","answer":"1\/2, -1\/3, -11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -16, -4, -8, -2, -3.","answer":"-16, -8, -4, -3, -2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -1, -2, 0.89, 0.1, -0.3.","answer":"-2, -1, -0.3, 0.1, 0.89","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -4, 616, -10, 2, 5 in decreasing order.","answer":"616, 5, 2, -4, -10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 1\/3, 0.5, 0.1, 7 in increasing order.","answer":"0.1, 1\/3, 0.5, 7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 3, 16, 0, 21.","answer":"0, 3, 16, 21","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -4, 252, 4 in decreasing order.","answer":"252, 4, -4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 11, 1, -1, 0, 5 in ascending order.","answer":"-1, 0, 1, 5, 11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -16, -2, 0 in increasing order.","answer":"-16, -2, 0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -5, 0.1, 1441 in decreasing order.","answer":"1441, 0.1, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -52, 2, -4, 3, -5 in descending order.","answer":"3, 2, -4, -5, -52","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 34, -5, -4 in decreasing order.","answer":"34, -4, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 4, -2, 3, -36.","answer":"-36, -2, 3, 4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 0.1, 1\/3, -1 in ascending order.","answer":"-1, 0.1, 1\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 420, 0, 4 in increasing order.","answer":"0, 4, 420","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort 1\/3, 69, 1\/4 in decreasing order.","answer":"69, 1\/3, 1\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -18, -12, -4 in increasing order.","answer":"-18, -12, -4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 0, 5, -1, -2, -212 in descending order.","answer":"5, 0, -1, -2, -212","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 2, -3, 0, -57 in decreasing order.","answer":"2, 0, -3, -57","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 17, -3, 0, -133 in descending order.","answer":"17, 0, -3, -133","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many minutes are there in 13\/8 of a week?","answer":"16380.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many kilograms are there in seventy-five halves of a tonne?","answer":"37500.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millilitres are there in six fifths of a litre?","answer":"1200.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many micrograms are there in 0.1586889 milligrams?","answer":"158.6889","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 2.112301 millilitres to litres.","answer":"0.002112301","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many grams are there in eleven eighths of a kilogram?","answer":"1375.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many nanometers are there in twenty-five halves of a micrometer?","answer":"12500.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many kilometers are there in 57.27808m?","answer":"0.05727808","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many centimeters are there in 0.0982382 nanometers?","answer":"9.82382e-09","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many decades are there in twenty-nine fifths of a century?","answer":"58.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 80319.95 kilograms to micrograms.","answer":"80319950000000","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 5.92509 litres to millilitres.","answer":"5925.09","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millennia are there in 15739.6 centuries?","answer":"1573.96","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is five quarters of a litre in millilitres?","answer":"1250.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many months are there in seven eighths of a millennium?","answer":"10500.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many nanograms are there in 3\/5 of a microgram?","answer":"600.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 0.9008868 litres in millilitres?","answer":"900.8868","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 6.877596 millilitres to litres.","answer":"0.006877596","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many centuries are there in 6.312342 decades?","answer":"0.6312342","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many kilometers are there in 791701.7 nanometers?","answer":"0.0000007917017","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is three eighths of a litre in millilitres?","answer":"375.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many nanoseconds are there in 3505.01 microseconds?","answer":"3505010.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many years are there in 0.4903807 centuries?","answer":"49.03807","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many centuries are there in 27\/5 of a millennium?","answer":"54.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 1183.053 meters in nanometers?","answer":"1183053000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 15\/4 of a gram in milligrams?","answer":"3750","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is fifty-five halves of a kilometer in meters?","answer":"27500.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millilitres are there in one twentieth of a litre?","answer":"50.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many seconds are there in 23\/3 of a minute?","answer":"460.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 3\/16 of a kilometer in centimeters?","answer":"18750.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 204.507m in micrometers?","answer":"204507000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many grams are there in one twentieth of a tonne?","answer":"50000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 711.957 months to millennia.","answer":"0.05932975","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 3\/32 of a kilometer in centimeters?","answer":"9375.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many meters are there in 84353.36nm?","answer":"8.435336e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is fifty-one halves of a centimeter in millimeters?","answer":"255","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 881199.5l to millilitres.","answer":"881199500.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many centuries are there in 0.4701828 millennia?","answer":"4.701828","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is three eighths of a kilogram in grams?","answer":"375.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 18.147 meters to nanometers.","answer":"18147000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 0.5016751 tonnes to kilograms.","answer":"501.6751","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 6.254496 decades in centuries?","answer":"0.6254496","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many grams are there in five eighths of a kilogram?","answer":"625.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 16\/15 of a century in months?","answer":"1280.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many microseconds are there in 924.743 nanoseconds?","answer":"0.924743","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 0.7893657 millennia to centuries.","answer":"7.893657","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 8260.556 days in nanoseconds?","answer":"7.137120384e+17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is fourty-three thirds of a century in months?","answer":"17200.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many minutes are there in twenty-two ninths of a week?","answer":"24640.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 2\/125 of a meter in millimeters?","answer":"16","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 556880.9 micrograms in nanograms?","answer":"556880900.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 36065.45 decades to millennia.","answer":"360.6545","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millimeters are there in eleven tenths of a centimeter?","answer":"11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millennia are there in 46.56995 decades?","answer":"0.4656995","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 0.929527 centuries in millennia?","answer":"0.0929527","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 57786.15l in millilitres?","answer":"57786150.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 196400.6 years in decades?","answer":"19640.06","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many decades are there in 51\/2 of a century?","answer":"255.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many microseconds are there in thirteen quarters of a millisecond?","answer":"3250.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many micrograms are there in 99.86595 milligrams?","answer":"99865.95","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many years are there in fifteen quarters of a century?","answer":"375.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is one tenth of a milligram in nanograms?","answer":"100000","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 310 minutes before 3:15 AM?","answer":"10:05 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 1:44 PM and 4:22 PM?","answer":"158","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 6:56 PM and 5:27 AM?","answer":"631","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 587 minutes after 11:38 PM?","answer":"9:25 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 589 minutes before 10:29 AM?","answer":"12:40 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 4:04 AM and 9:31 AM?","answer":"327","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 135 minutes before 3:39 AM?","answer":"1:24 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 38 minutes before 8:34 AM?","answer":"7:56 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 1:30 PM and 11:50 PM?","answer":"620","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 714 minutes after 6:33 PM?","answer":"6:27 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 19 minutes after 5:27 AM?","answer":"5:46 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 5:23 AM and 1:34 PM?","answer":"491","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 207 minutes before 11:55 AM?","answer":"8:28 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 185 minutes after 2:58 PM?","answer":"6:03 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 685 minutes after 9:30 AM?","answer":"8:55 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 6:01 AM and 5:20 PM?","answer":"679","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 3:51 PM and 10:17 PM?","answer":"386","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 7:45 PM and 12:47 AM?","answer":"302","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 41 minutes before 5:35 PM?","answer":"4:54 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 1:38 AM and 4:00 AM?","answer":"142","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 404 minutes before 2:27 PM?","answer":"7:43 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 4:46 PM and 1:44 AM?","answer":"538","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 10:52 PM and 5:53 AM?","answer":"421","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 504 minutes after 10:24 AM?","answer":"6:48 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 1:03 PM and 9:11 PM?","answer":"488","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 6:58 AM and 3:21 PM?","answer":"503","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 5:40 AM and 10:06 AM?","answer":"266","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 10:54 PM and 11:36 PM?","answer":"42","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 254 minutes before 3:37 PM?","answer":"11:23 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 240 minutes after 1:02 AM?","answer":"5:02 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 92 minutes after 4:09 PM?","answer":"5:41 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 286 minutes after 5:45 PM?","answer":"10:31 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 38 minutes after 1:01 PM?","answer":"1:39 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 7:51 PM and 1:32 AM?","answer":"341","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 2:35 AM and 12:55 PM?","answer":"620","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 3:59 PM and 5:30 PM?","answer":"91","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 354 minutes before 10:50 AM?","answer":"4:56 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 63 minutes after 8:39 PM?","answer":"9:42 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 52 minutes before 8:59 PM?","answer":"8:07 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 10:07 AM and 3:07 PM?","answer":"300","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 243 minutes after 6:33 AM?","answer":"10:36 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 4:09 PM and 3:58 AM?","answer":"709","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 4:46 PM and 8:43 PM?","answer":"237","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 526 minutes after 6:59 AM?","answer":"3:45 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 9 minutes before 10:13 PM?","answer":"10:04 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 7:17 PM and 4:35 AM?","answer":"558","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 3:57 PM and 10:43 PM?","answer":"406","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 240 minutes after 9:49 PM?","answer":"1:49 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 607 minutes after 9:30 PM?","answer":"7:37 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 11:14 AM and 10:16 PM?","answer":"662","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 250 minutes after 3:38 AM?","answer":"7:48 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 11:19 AM and 4:39 PM?","answer":"320","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 583 minutes before 12:57 AM?","answer":"3:14 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 277 minutes after 10:50 AM?","answer":"3:27 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 12:35 AM and 9:30 AM?","answer":"535","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 11:01 PM and 8:25 AM?","answer":"564","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 1:36 AM and 12:36 PM?","answer":"660","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 609 minutes after 10:14 AM?","answer":"8:23 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 609 minutes before 7:01 AM?","answer":"8:52 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 10:10 PM and 9:47 AM?","answer":"697","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 552 minutes after 5:36 PM?","answer":"2:48 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 372 minutes after 6:04 PM?","answer":"12:16 AM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 391 is divided by 18?","answer":"13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 6196 is divided by 50.","answer":"46","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 156 is divided by 57?","answer":"42","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 235 is divided by 80?","answer":"75","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1902 is divided by 901.","answer":"100","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1221 is divided by 163.","answer":"80","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 63 is divided by 16.","answer":"15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 151 is divided by 116?","answer":"35","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1468 is divided by 7.","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 35 is divided by 18.","answer":"17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 2198 is divided by 44?","answer":"42","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 3914 is divided by 15?","answer":"14","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 622 is divided by 125?","answer":"122","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 752 is divided by 75.","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 132 is divided by 46.","answer":"40","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 418 is divided by 10.","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 444 is divided by 33.","answer":"15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 249 is divided by 47.","answer":"14","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 930 is divided by 117?","answer":"111","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 50 is divided by 18?","answer":"14","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 142 is divided by 38?","answer":"28","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 699 is divided by 35.","answer":"34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 155 is divided by 23?","answer":"17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 3564 is divided by 356.","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 28 is divided by 15?","answer":"13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 1260 is divided by 233?","answer":"95","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 129 is divided by 61?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 3440 is divided by 855?","answer":"20","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 78 is divided by 8.","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 60 is divided by 5.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1196 is divided by 38.","answer":"18","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 2389 is divided by 92?","answer":"89","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 233 is divided by 77?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 4982 is divided by 86?","answer":"80","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 327 is divided by 82?","answer":"81","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 316 is divided by 31?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 411 is divided by 83?","answer":"79","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 226 is divided by 219?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 20 is divided by 11.","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1088 is divided by 19.","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 147 is divided by 23.","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 168 is divided by 27.","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1102 is divided by 326.","answer":"124","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 658 is divided by 75.","answer":"58","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 91 is divided by 1?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 154 is divided by 40?","answer":"34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 158 is divided by 31.","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 685 is divided by 226?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 319 is divided by 109.","answer":"101","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 4217 is divided by 19.","answer":"18","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 1061 is divided by 38?","answer":"35","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 255 is divided by 20?","answer":"15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 113 is divided by 13.","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 651 is divided by 112.","answer":"91","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 12707 is divided by 71.","answer":"69","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 956 is divided by 287?","answer":"95","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 657 is divided by 16?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 39054 is divided by 535.","answer":"534","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 33 is divided by 4?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 1158 is divided by 25?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 682 is divided by 18.","answer":"16","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 3495 is divided by 135?","answer":"120","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 9477 and 273.","answer":"39","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 70 and 1610?","answer":"70","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 26 and 702?","answer":"26","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 570 and 38?","answer":"38","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 2230 and 30?","answer":"10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 418 and 22?","answer":"22","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 38 and 171?","answer":"19","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 4608 and 36.","answer":"36","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 1507 and 198?","answer":"11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 177 and 59?","answer":"59","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 48 and 1520?","answer":"16","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 90 and 144.","answer":"18","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common divisor of 342 and 18.","answer":"18","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 1862 and 98.","answer":"98","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 54 and 1809?","answer":"27","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 120 and 36?","answer":"12","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 158 and 52930?","answer":"158","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 17797 and 13.","answer":"13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common divisor of 600 and 1680.","answer":"120","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 800 and 350?","answer":"50","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 117 and 65.","answer":"13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 32 and 20?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 2222 and 55.","answer":"11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common divisor of 16 and 4.","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 800 and 325.","answer":"25","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 30 and 16690.","answer":"10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 5037 and 69?","answer":"69","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 7 and 21?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 3549 and 42.","answer":"21","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 7410 and 104.","answer":"26","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 6 and 1497?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 12 and 102?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 100 and 4?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common divisor of 299 and 23.","answer":"23","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 105 and 2058?","answer":"21","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 53 and 53?","answer":"53","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 5 and 640.","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 10 and 1070?","answer":"10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 75 and 390?","answer":"15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 44 and 154.","answer":"22","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 8943 and 66.","answer":"33","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 17856 and 16?","answer":"16","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 1370 and 450.","answer":"10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 104 and 351?","answer":"13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 810 and 6615?","answer":"135","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common divisor of 7 and 2.","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 779 and 95?","answer":"19","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 303 and 12.","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 506 and 1748.","answer":"46","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 95 and 5?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 56 and 14?","answer":"14","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 1392 and 48.","answer":"48","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 65 and 1625.","answer":"65","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 32 and 55?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 66 and 294?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 21342 and 12.","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 867 and 408?","answer":"51","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 32 and 7376?","answer":"16","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 198 and 110?","answer":"22","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 4 and 716?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 2255 and 495.","answer":"55","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common factor of 338 and 130.","answer":"26","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of 11\/45 and -3\/335?","answer":"3015","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -87\/704 and -14\/187.","answer":"11968","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 33 and 408?","answer":"4488","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 44 and 16?","answer":"176","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -99\/140 and -113\/30.","answer":"420","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of 71\/2244 and 83\/1428.","answer":"15708","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of 32\/145 and 28\/23.","answer":"3335","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 245 and 5495?","answer":"38465","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 53\/33 and 58\/231.","answer":"231","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 115\/24 and -131\/576.","answer":"576","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the least common multiple of 6728 and 40?","answer":"33640","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 139\/2640 and -109\/660.","answer":"2640","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the least common multiple of 5061 and 42.","answer":"10122","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the least common multiple of 90 and 288?","answer":"1440","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -43\/9 and 5\/1494.","answer":"1494","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of 15\/8 and 97\/416?","answer":"416","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of -82\/2415 and -109\/8970?","answer":"62790","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of 62\/9 and -19\/1892?","answer":"17028","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -59\/8 and 25\/88.","answer":"88","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the least common multiple of 24498 and 8.","answer":"97992","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 12 and 8?","answer":"24","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of -16\/35 and -76\/39.","answer":"1365","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 20 and 8?","answer":"40","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 525 and 35?","answer":"525","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -4\/57 and 47\/54.","answer":"1026","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of 17\/156 and 113\/572.","answer":"1716","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of -93\/58 and -5\/58?","answer":"58","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 3 and 325?","answer":"975","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 157\/60 and 103\/50.","answer":"300","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -139\/350 and 151\/210.","answer":"1050","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the lowest common multiple of 48 and 36.","answer":"144","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the lowest common multiple of 298 and 2.","answer":"298","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the least common multiple of 10 and 5?","answer":"10","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of -1\/8 and 99\/10.","answer":"40","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 107\/12 and -25\/4.","answer":"12","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 44 and 176?","answer":"176","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the lowest common multiple of 1368 and 1368.","answer":"1368","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the smallest common multiple of 7272 and 909.","answer":"7272","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the lowest common multiple of 1355 and 80.","answer":"21680","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the smallest common multiple of 286 and 364.","answer":"4004","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the smallest common multiple of 66 and 1572.","answer":"17292","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 24 and 24?","answer":"24","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of 83\/14 and -41\/6.","answer":"42","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of 15\/746 and -67\/1492?","answer":"1492","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -79\/222 and -7\/1776.","answer":"1776","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the smallest common multiple of 22 and 12.","answer":"132","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the least common multiple of 5480 and 40.","answer":"5480","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 196 and 6?","answer":"588","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of -125\/1278 and -79\/4.","answer":"2556","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the least common multiple of 112 and 182.","answer":"1456","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the smallest common multiple of 40 and 230.","answer":"920","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the least common multiple of 19567 and 12661.","answer":"215237","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -47\/10 and 19\/681.","answer":"6810","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of -59\/120 and -29\/24?","answer":"120","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of 40\/119 and 29\/28.","answer":"476","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of 115\/582 and -4\/11.","answer":"6402","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 330 and 180?","answer":"1980","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 8093 and 3?","answer":"24279","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 34\/63 and 54\/7.","answer":"63","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the lowest common multiple of 34 and 816.","answer":"816","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the common denominator of 83\/34 and 41\/17?","answer":"34","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of 8\/77 and 37\/33.","answer":"231","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 2648.","answer":"2, 331","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 605?","answer":"5, 11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 10396?","answer":"2, 23, 113","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 194?","answer":"2, 97","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 77887.","answer":"71, 1097","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 5181.","answer":"3, 11, 157","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 1409.","answer":"1409","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 16617?","answer":"3, 29, 191","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 572.","answer":"2, 11, 13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 7280?","answer":"2, 5, 7, 13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 5809?","answer":"37, 157","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 245.","answer":"5, 7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 50103?","answer":"3, 19, 293","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 86115.","answer":"3, 5, 5741","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 85718.","answer":"2, 42859","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 3830.","answer":"2, 5, 383","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 4694?","answer":"2, 2347","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 3329.","answer":"3329","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 2148.","answer":"2, 3, 179","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 5213?","answer":"13, 401","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 17477.","answer":"17477","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 1537?","answer":"29, 53","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 127.","answer":"127","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 1914.","answer":"2, 3, 11, 29","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 18177?","answer":"3, 73, 83","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 153?","answer":"3, 17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 13803?","answer":"3, 43, 107","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 10563?","answer":"3, 7, 503","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 1700?","answer":"2, 5, 17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 6320?","answer":"2, 5, 79","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 33407.","answer":"11, 3037","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 2451?","answer":"3, 19, 43","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 79089.","answer":"3, 41, 643","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 40984?","answer":"2, 47, 109","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 1243?","answer":"11, 113","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 9713.","answer":"11, 883","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 690.","answer":"2, 3, 5, 23","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 15653.","answer":"11, 1423","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 2080.","answer":"2, 5, 13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 118315?","answer":"5, 23663","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 30943.","answer":"11, 29, 97","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 192015.","answer":"3, 5, 17, 251","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 1177.","answer":"11, 107","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 12333?","answer":"3, 4111","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 757.","answer":"757","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 68166?","answer":"2, 3, 7, 541","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 7793.","answer":"7793","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 17177?","answer":"89, 193","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 10332?","answer":"2, 3, 7, 41","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 8677?","answer":"8677","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 7298.","answer":"2, 41, 89","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 17064.","answer":"2, 3, 79","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 36396.","answer":"2, 3, 337","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 20232.","answer":"2, 3, 281","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 56939.","answer":"97, 587","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 14164?","answer":"2, 3541","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 127023?","answer":"3, 13, 3257","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 722.","answer":"2, 19","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 54552?","answer":"2, 3, 2273","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 1349.","answer":"19, 71","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 987?","answer":"3, 7, 47","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 1125.","answer":"3, 5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 21679?","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 456?","answer":"6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 29409?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 2446?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 3521?","answer":"2.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 1455?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 174?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 1275?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the ten thousands digit of 112150?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 1787?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 12116?","answer":"6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 6747?","answer":"7.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 361?","answer":"6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the ten thousands digit of 55658?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 10668?","answer":"6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 5113?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 3526?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 17587?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 2908?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 168718?","answer":"8.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 3684?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 289?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 2194?","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 3702?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 3248?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 959?","answer":"9.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 3848?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 9001?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 445?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 1583?","answer":"5.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 55857?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 6621?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 7420?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 17349?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 16543?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 250?","answer":"2.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 72831?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 75271?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 804?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 3093?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 3202?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 232?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 1155?","answer":"1.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 3804?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 3406?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 1057?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 3348?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 7358?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 16633?","answer":"6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 72672?","answer":"2.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 60986?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the ten thousands digit of 29469?","answer":"2.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 5546?","answer":"4.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 840?","answer":"4.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 1599?","answer":"9.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 66433?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 4242?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 4609?","answer":"9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the thousands digit of 1814?","answer":"1","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 6041?","answer":"1.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 7577?","answer":"7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 30741?","answer":"7.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -0.00008463 to 5 dps.","answer":"-8e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -884.33 to the nearest integer.","answer":"-884.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -0.035847 to two dps.","answer":"-0.04","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -521.67 rounded to the nearest 100?","answer":"-500.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -0.00015043 to 4 decimal places.","answer":"-0.0002","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -0.26108 to 1 decimal place.","answer":"-0.3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 3907 rounded to the nearest one hundred?","answer":"3900.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -204.7 rounded to the nearest ten?","answer":"-200.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.0033478 rounded to five decimal places?","answer":"0.00335","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -231480 to the nearest ten thousand.","answer":"-230000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 15504000 to the nearest one million.","answer":"16000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.0000006669 rounded to 7 dps?","answer":"7e-07","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 927310 to the nearest 1000.","answer":"927000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.000198 rounded to 5 decimal places?","answer":"0.0002","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -7.35 to zero decimal places.","answer":"-7.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 0.00006507 to five decimal places.","answer":"7e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 36760000 rounded to the nearest one million?","answer":"37000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 17537.3 to the nearest 1000.","answer":"18000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.0008791 rounded to five dps?","answer":"-0.00088","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.00021903 rounded to 5 decimal places?","answer":"0.00022","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -477.2 rounded to the nearest 10?","answer":"-480.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 19.84 rounded to 1 decimal place?","answer":"19.8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -14.13 rounded to the nearest ten?","answer":"-10.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.000039 rounded to six dps?","answer":"3.9e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.000001115 rounded to seven dps?","answer":"1.1e-06","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 111605 to the nearest ten thousand.","answer":"110000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.57208 rounded to 1 dp?","answer":"0.6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 4117.6 to the nearest 10.","answer":"4120.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.00007368 rounded to 6 dps?","answer":"7.4e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -72.79 to the nearest integer.","answer":"-73.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -375.37 rounded to the nearest one hundred?","answer":"-400.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 1264.71 rounded to the nearest 10?","answer":"1260.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.082013 rounded to 4 decimal places?","answer":"-0.082","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -333690 rounded to the nearest 1000?","answer":"-334000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 276630 rounded to the nearest 10000?","answer":"280000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 3100000 to the nearest one million.","answer":"3000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -69.545 to one dp.","answer":"-69.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 5.706 to one dp.","answer":"5.7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.0001043 rounded to 5 decimal places?","answer":"-0.0001","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.11795 rounded to 3 decimal places?","answer":"0.118","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 46480000 to the nearest 1000000.","answer":"46000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.01007 rounded to 2 dps?","answer":"-0.01","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -7890.7 to the nearest one hundred.","answer":"-7900.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -119 rounded to the nearest 100?","answer":"-100.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 0.000037295 to six dps.","answer":"3.7e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 1428 rounded to the nearest one hundred?","answer":"1400.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.00158701 rounded to 5 dps?","answer":"0.00159","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.006264 rounded to 4 dps?","answer":"-0.0063","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 236370 rounded to the nearest ten thousand?","answer":"240000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -491.93 rounded to 0 dps?","answer":"-492.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 1402 to the nearest 100.","answer":"1400.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.27868 rounded to two decimal places?","answer":"-0.28","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -435000 rounded to the nearest one hundred thousand?","answer":"-400000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 85.76 to the nearest integer.","answer":"86.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 13.5 to the nearest 10.","answer":"10.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -25386000 to the nearest one million.","answer":"-25000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 0.000010662 to seven dps.","answer":"1.07e-05","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 0.3246 to two dps.","answer":"0.32","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -1.319 rounded to 1 decimal place?","answer":"-1.3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -0.40848 to one dp.","answer":"-0.4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 0.0100242 to 3 dps.","answer":"0.01","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -892.7 rounded to the nearest 10?","answer":"-890.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Sum -3.24 and 375.","answer":"371.76","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -13900 rounded to the nearest ten thousand?","answer":"-10000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out 1035283 + -2.","answer":"1035281.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in -609, -1221, -1833?","answer":"-2445","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 562 is divided by 4.","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is the value of ((-84)\/490)\/((-4)\/10)?","answer":"3\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 831?","answer":"3, 277","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Calculate 13601*-0.5.","answer":"-6800.5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
